

MARKO **GOLUBOVIĆ**

QA TESTER



ABOUT

Meticulous, neat, detailed person in real life, so that's how I work on a computer. I am a normal person, suggestions and criticisms encourage me to work harder.

Well-mannered, I know how to say good day, goodbye and thank you, maybe it's funny that I emphasize this, but taught by experience, I think it's worth emphasizing.

More about me on the next link:

max-developing.com



CONTACT

ILIJE KORAĆA 6, BEOGRAD

Address

+381 65 805 24 28
Phone number

marko94golubovic@gmail.com E-mail

29.10.1994. Date of birth



EDUCATION

BACHELOR OF ECONOMICS

John Naisbitt University 2013 - 2017

ECONOMIC TECHNICIAN

Fifth economic school, Rakovica 2009 - 2013



LANGUAGES

SERBIAN Native

ENGLISH

В2



WORK EXPERIENCE

ACUMENICS

QA Tester

Accruent (Expesite.com)

December 2020 - Present

Writting test cases in qTest, updating tickets in Jira's agile board, updating Confluence page, creating test cycles and testing plans, regression and exploratory tests on lower and higher environments, working with SQL Databases, executing the scripts on lower environments in SQL Databases, daily Scrum meetings, analyzing clients requirements.

DOCUMENICS

Accountant

July 2019 - December 2020

Accurate maintenance of financial systems including: Journal Entries (Payroll, period end accruals, etc.)

Processing of Accounts Payable invoices and timely completion of monthly accruals.

Posting daiy sales in General Ledger.
Processing accounting receivables.
Conduct monthly reconciliation of bank accounts.
Conduct periodic reconciliations of accounts to ensure their accuracy.
Perform other accounting tasks as requested by Client (Only US Clients) or
Documenics management from time to time

CINEPLEXX Accountant

July 2016 - April 2019

Recording, checking and correcting invoices, alongside creating and issuing them to private and legal entities. Creating and updating cost reporst, performing invoice payment, work hour checks and salary payment to employees. Executing paid market checks for all organizational units, submitting necessary information to relevant accounting agencies and gift voucher issues resolution.



_	S	/	I I	
	\circ	\sim	╵┕	LO

HTML

CSS

Sass

jQuery

JavaScript

Figma

GitHub

Git

MS Office

Photoshop

Fiddler

npm



COURSES

HTML, CSS3

Sass, Bootstrap

JavaScript

Udemy

W3Schools